<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Real Estate &#8211; NR Constructions</title>
	<atom:link href="http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/category/real-estate/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp</link>
	<description>Your Trust Is Our Reputation</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 14:29:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/nr-favicon-logo.png</url>
	<title>Real Estate &#8211; NR Constructions</title>
	<link>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Best Home Loan Interest Rates in India 2020</title>
		<link>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/20/best-home-loan-interest-rates-in-india-2020/</link>
					<comments>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/20/best-home-loan-interest-rates-in-india-2020/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nrconstructions]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 07:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/?p=1461</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To what extent have you been living in a leased house in the city of your work? Tired of moving from house to house? Why not accepting your own fantasy home in 2020 when such a large number of banks are prepared to give you a Best Home Loan as indicated by your own needs! &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/20/best-home-loan-interest-rates-in-india-2020/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Best Home Loan Interest Rates in India 2020</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>To what extent have you been living in a leased house in the city of your work? Tired of moving from house to house? Why not accepting your own fantasy home in 2020 when such a large number of banks are prepared to give you a Best Home Loan as indicated by your own needs!</p>



<h4><strong>Special Rates for Women</strong></h4>



<p>Banks offer inclination to ladies borrowers as they are seen to be increasingly dependable, and will in general get lower home advance loan fees. Ladies can likewise apply for home advances with lesser qualification models and pick longer residencies for reimbursement. Stamp obligation and different assessments are likewise lower for ladies. Post the dispatch of repo-connected home advances.</p>



<h4><strong>Our projects approved by ICICI, HDFC</strong></h4>



<h6><strong>Few things to know while applying for housing loan</strong></h6>



<ul><li>Home loan interest rates.</li><li>Monthly EMI&#8217;s.</li><li>Eligibility Criteria.</li><li>Self/Salaried/Government Employee benefits.</li><li>Loan tenure.</li><li>Home loan benefits for women.</li><li>Benefits for first time buyers.</li><li>Difference between NBFC  and Bank interest rates.</li><li>Difference between floating interest and fixed interest.</li><li>Foreclosure charges for closing the bank loan.</li></ul>



<p>Apply for loan in ICICI bank. <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.icicibank.com/Personal-Banking/loans/home-loan/home-loan-interest-rates.page#" target="_blank">Click Here</a></p>



<p>Apply for loan in HDFC bank. <a href="https://www.hdfc.com/housing-loans/home-loans" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Click Here</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/20/best-home-loan-interest-rates-in-india-2020/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Benefits of Buying Ready to Occupy flats in Guntur, Andhra Pradesh</title>
		<link>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/15/benefits-of-buying-ready-to-occupy-flats-in-guntur/</link>
					<comments>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/15/benefits-of-buying-ready-to-occupy-flats-in-guntur/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nrconstructions]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 08:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/?p=1451</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A lot of thought needs to be put in before buying an apartment. In a city like Guntur, Andhra Pradesh, where the real estate industry is in starting stage and lots of choices for good investment and you can get good returns in less time, it’s common to have a confusion on what kind of &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/15/benefits-of-buying-ready-to-occupy-flats-in-guntur/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Benefits of Buying Ready to Occupy flats in Guntur, Andhra Pradesh</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A lot of thought needs to be put in before buying an apartment. In a city like Guntur, Andhra Pradesh, where the real estate industry is in starting stage and lots of choices for good investment and you can get good returns in less time, it’s common to have a confusion on what kind of apartment to choose. Generally, people tend to be confused whether to buy a ready to occupy flats or prelaunch ones. Prelaunch properties might take a longer time for completion than expected. This can cause lots of difficulties and frustration to the buyer. Similarly, there are no guarantee that whatever promised would be delivered. This is the reason why you should consider investing on ready to occupy flats. Let’s take a look at some advantages of buying ready to occupy flats.</p>



<h4><strong>Ready to Occupy Flats Ensure Quality</strong></h4>



<p>When you spend a large sum of money into a property, it’s essential to make sure that it has quality. In the case of prelaunch properties, you can’t be really sure whether the flat will be delivered with the quality that they promised. Similarly, the flat may lack amenities that are essential. But when you choose to buy ready to occupy flats, you have the advantage of seeing the flat as it is. You get to see with your own eyes what facilities are available and the overall quality of the property. This gives you a reassurance that the money you are spending is worth it.</p>



<h4><strong>Saving Time and money</strong></h4>



<ul><li>Ready to occupy flats don&#8217;t have per EMI&#8217;s.</li><li>GST and tax benefits make an attractive proposition.</li><li>No Waiting time.</li><li>No risk of project getting delayed.</li><li>Once the property is ready to occupy stage that means it has a occupancy certificate mentioning that there is no flaws in the construction.</li><li>Can check all the amenities mentioned by the contractor.</li><li>Can Verify your neighbors.</li></ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/15/benefits-of-buying-ready-to-occupy-flats-in-guntur/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why NR Constructions ?</title>
		<link>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/15/why-nr-constructions/</link>
					<comments>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/15/why-nr-constructions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nrconstructions]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 08:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/?p=1448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Vast Experience in Real estate since 1991. Eco Friendly Constructions with natural materials. Latest Technologies. Great Amenities. 100% Vasthu. Security Security comes to begin with. We offer a secure working environment for everybody working on, going by, or working close our job sites. Quality We’ll meet your desires, at that point we’ll surpass them. Our &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/15/why-nr-constructions/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Why NR Constructions ?</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul><li>Vast Experience in Real estate since 1991.</li><li>Eco Friendly Constructions with natural materials.</li><li>Latest Technologies.</li><li>Great Amenities.</li><li>100% Vasthu.</li></ul>



<h4>Security</h4>



<p>Security comes to begin with. We offer a secure working environment for everybody working on, going by, or working close our job sites.</p>



<h4>Quality</h4>



<p class="has-text-align-left">We’ll meet your desires, at that point we’ll surpass them. Our group individuals will demonstrate themselves to you through the victory and the quality of your venture.</p>



<h4>Customer Service</h4>



<p class="has-text-align-left">We ceaselessly improve our preparation, instruments and procedures to expand the nature of administration we give our customers.</p>



<h4>Integrity</h4>



<p class="has-text-align-left">Your best interest is our solely interest. And we’ll move forward exploitation our company’s core values to determine mutual trust, and provides you what you would like.</p>



<h4>Teamwork</h4>



<p class="has-text-align-left">We’re the industry pioneer for a reason – we empower our group individuals to work together to illuminate each single development challenge we confront.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/15/why-nr-constructions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lockdown: Is it Right time for Real Estate Investment</title>
		<link>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/13/lockdown-is-it-right-time-for-real-estate-investment/</link>
					<comments>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/13/lockdown-is-it-right-time-for-real-estate-investment/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nrconstructions]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 13:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/?p=1356</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nobody in the nation never envisioned such a lockdown circumstance, as this pandemic COVID-19 making a frenzy circumstance over the globe. The sort of news showing up in the news channels, papers, and online life; however do we all need to envision, listening crown flare-up or need to see this lockdown is a chance to &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/13/lockdown-is-it-right-time-for-real-estate-investment/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Lockdown: Is it Right time for Real Estate Investment</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Nobody in the nation never envisioned such a lockdown circumstance, as this pandemic COVID-19 making a frenzy circumstance over the globe. The sort of news showing up in the news channels, papers, and online life; however do we all need to envision, listening crown flare-up or need to see this lockdown is a chance to investigate increasingly extravagant future. These vulnerabilities are constantly surprising. So how about we be set up for a solid future.</p>



<h4><strong>Things being what they are, Are you arranged?</strong></h4>



<p>We need you to use this opportunity to investigate more to put resources into various wellsprings of easy revenue, positively, this is the correct time to comprehend conceivable speculation choices accessible around us where we can give automated revenue and secure our future in a dubious circumstance to defend.</p>



<p>In spite of the fact that there are alternatives like SIP, Mutual Funds, Stocks, and so forth., at that point why not Real Estate. Land is demonstrated as one of the dependable speculation choice, which goes about as steady and safe.</p>



<h4><strong>Why Real Estate in the Lockdown Period?</strong></h4>



<p>Most of the individuals are holding their choices to purchase land until the lockdown lifts by the Government because of hypothesis/hazard/financial conditions. Yet, Savvy Investors are intently watching the present economic situations and exploiting current circumstances and moving cleverly.</p>



<h4><strong>Why should you act smart in this period?</strong></h4>



<h4><strong>Demand:</strong></h4>



<p>As the Real Estate confronting little shortfall popular in the present economic situations which prompts producing different alluring ideas by the Developers as far as appealing costs, rewarding installment plans and any extra offers, which at last goes advantage to the Customers.</p>



<h4><strong>REPO Rate:</strong></h4>



<p>We are seen that RBI has declared in the decrease of REPO Rate .75% and new base rate 4.4%, this will prompts a decrease on low-loan cost by at any rate .75%. This would be an extra advantage to the Customers whoever purchases a Property now.</p>



<h4><strong>Income:</strong></h4>



<p>Land purchasing is constantly a sheltered speculation. This is again a chance to make a different resource portfolio and start another wellspring of automated revenue</p>



<h4><strong>Opportunity:</strong></h4>



<p>Because of low interest, clients get a favorable position to benefit of good inventories at an appealing rate. When things begin settling the extent of arrangement will lessen and request will rise. There is no uncertainty the rate won&#8217;t be as low as they are currently during this lockdown period.</p>



<h4><strong>Don’t Miss:</strong></h4>



<p>This is an ideal opportunity to design your speculation to increase broad profits for the venture, bring down the cost of the property and exceptional yield on your speculation.</p>



<h4><strong>Brand to associate:</strong></h4>



<p>In spite of the fact that it is a fantastic chance to purchase a Real Estate now, you generally have bounteous choices to go with &#8216;A&#8217; classification manufacturer. During this lockdown, you have extra time to do your tirelessness about different activities, area, manufacturer, regard possibilities of the Real Estate and success.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://dineshreddyalla.github.io/githubwp/2020/05/13/lockdown-is-it-right-time-for-real-estate-investment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
